(this.webpackJsonppopculturequiz=this.webpackJsonppopculturequiz||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,function(e,a,i){},,,function(e,a,i){e.exports=i(15)},,,,,function(e,a,i){},function(e,a,i){},function(e,a,i){"use strict";i.r(a);var t=i(0),n=i.n(t),o=i(7),s=i.n(o),r=(i(13),i(14),i(1)),h=i(2),l=i(4),u=i(3),d=(i(5),[{question:"What is alterego of Batman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Bruce Wayne",id:121},{question:"What is Earth Name of Superman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Clark kent",id:122},{question:"Who has the invisible jet?",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Diana prince",id:123},{question:"Who is speedster died during crisis on infinite earths",options:["Bart Allen","Wally West","Barry Allen","Jay Garrick"],answer:"Barry Allen",id:124},{question:"What is alterego of Aquaman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Arthur Curry"],answer:"Arthur Curry",id:125},{question:"Who is father of Batman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Thomas wayne","Arthur Curry"],answer:"Thomas wayne",id:126},{question:"Which Robin becomes Nightwing",options:["Dick grayson","Jason todd","Tim drake","Conner kent"],answer:"Dick grayson",id:127},{question:"What is alterego of Cyborg",options:["Victor Stone","Jason todd","Tim drake","Conner kent"],answer:"Victor Stone",id:128},{question:"What is earth name of supergirl",options:["Kara Danvers","Carol danvers","Alex danvers","Barbara gordon"],answer:"Kara Danvers",id:129},{question:"Who is youngest robin",options:["Dick grayson","Jason todd","Tim drake","Damian wayne"],answer:"Damian wayne",id:130}]),c=[{question:"What is alterego of Superboy",options:["Clark kent","conner kent","clark junior","Thomas wayne"],answer:"conner kent",id:151},{question:"Who is also known as Hell Blazer",options:["Lucifer","John Constantine","Zatanna Zatara","Mazekin"],answer:"John Constantine",id:152},{question:"What is alterego of Swamp Thing",options:["Alex Danvers","Abby Arcane","Alec Holland","kara Danvers"],answer:"Alec Holland",id:153},{question:"What is alterego of Star Girl",options:["Courtney Whitmore","yolanda","violet","Donna Troy"],answer:"Courtney Whitmore",id:154},{question:"What is Elder Brother of Anti-Monitor",options:["Monitor","Perpetua","World Forger","Darkseid"],answer:"World Forger",id:155},{question:"Who is son of Darkseid",options:["scott free","orion","grail","stepphen wolf"],answer:"orion",id:156},{question:"Who is daughter of the Demon and a member of Teen Titans?",options:["Raven","star fire","wonder girl","bumble bee"],answer:"Raven",id:157},{question:"Where is the head quaters of league of Assassins located?",options:["Mount Rushmore","Nanda Parbat","Manhattan","New york"],answer:"Nanda Parbat",id:158},{question:"Who is head of League of Assassins?",options:["Talia Al ghul","Lady Shiva","Damian Wayne","Ra's Al Ghul"],answer:"Ra's Al Ghul",id:159},{question:"What is alter ego of mister miracle",options:["scott free","orion","micheal keaton","Jimmy olsen"],answer:"scott free",id:160}],m=[{question:"What is alterego of earth-9 dark knight ?",options:["Bruce wayne","selina kyle","Bryce wayne","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Bryce wayne",id:181},{question:"Who is the mother of the Monitor?",options:["perpetua","allwidow","grail","Mazekin"],answer:"perpetua",id:182},{question:"Who is speedster batman from dark multiverse's ?",options:["deathracer","Godspeed","grimripper","Reddeath"],answer:"Reddeath",id:183},{question:"What is alterego of Wild Cat?",options:["Courtney Whitmore","Ted Grant","Kent Nelson","Donna Troy"],answer:"Ted Grant",id:184},{question:"Who is daughter of Darkseid?",options:["Reddaughter","BigBarda","Grail","Allwiow"],answer:"Grail",id:185},{question:"What is the emotion that powers blue lantern rings?",options:["Will","Compassion","Hope","Greed"],answer:"Hope",id:186},{question:"Who is the First Human Green Lantern?",options:["Hall Jordan","John Stewart","Kyle Reyner","Alan Scott"],answer:"Alan Scott",id:187},{question:"What is alterego of DC's Punchline(Anti-Harley Quinn)?",options:["Alex","Alexis","Alec","Red Tool"],answer:"Alexis",id:188},{question:"Who is brother of Martian Manhunter?",options:["Malaque'k","Johnaqa'k","Malafa'k","megafa'k"],answer:"Malafa'k",id:189},{question:"Who is the only JL member escaped from Darkseid's omega beam?",options:["Batman","Superman","Wonder Woman","Flash"],answer:"Batman",id:190}];var p=[{question:"What is alterego of Nine Tails Fox",options:["Red Demon Fox","Kurama","Shukaku","Matatabi"],answer:"Kurama",id:321},{question:"In Fairy Tail, Natsu is a?",options:["Fire Wizard","Demon Slayer","Fire Dragon Slayer","Celeistial Wizard"],answer:"Fire Dragon Slayer",id:322},{question:"What is name of Eren's Titan Form",options:["Attack Titan","Founder Titan","Female Titan","Beast Titan"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:323},{question:"What is the original name of KIRA",options:["LLawliet","Light Yagami","Teru Mikami","Ryuk"],answer:"Light Yagami",id:324},{question:"Who is father of Goten",options:["Piccolo","Bruce Wayne","Vegeta","Goku"],answer:"Goku",id:325}],f=[{question:"In Naruto, how many ninja from Konoha went on to the third stage(after the preliminairies) of the Chunin Exams?",options:["Six","Five","Seven","Four"],answer:"Five",id:351},{question:"In Fairy Tail, who is the first guild master of Fairy Tail?",options:["Gildarts","Makarov Dreyar","Jose Porla","Mavis Vermillion"],answer:"Mavis Vermillion",id:352},{question:"In Demon Slayer, what is the name of Flame Hashira ",options:["Sakonji Urokodaki","Giyu Tomioka","Kyojuro Rengoku","Shinobu Kocho"],answer:"Kyojuro Rengoku",id:353},{question:"In Pokemon, which Pokemon is attached to Slowbro?",options:["Skarmory","Cloyster","Mantine","Shellder"],answer:"Shellder",id:354},{question:"In My Hero Academia, what is the name of Sir Nighteye's protege (Hint: Quirk-Permeation)",options:["Mirio Togata","Mei Hatsume","Tamaki Amajiki","Nejire Hado"],answer:"Mirio Togata",id:355}],w=[{question:"In Naruto, what is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",options:["Lotus of Destruction","Shadow Lotus","Primary Lotus","Fiery Lotus"],answer:"Primary Lotus",id:381},{question:"In Fairy Tail, what did Natsu say upon seeing Lisanna in Edolas?",options:["'It can't be you.'","'Hi, honey. I'm home.'","'How? You're dead!'","'I found you.'"],answer:"'I found you.'",id:382},{question:"In Attack on Titan, Eren\u2019s nickname in the 104th Training Squad is what?",options:[" Captain Suicide","Rage Machine","Captain Rage","Suicidal Bastard"],answer:"Suicidal Bastard",id:383},{question:"In Death Note, what happens if you accidentally misspel victim's name four times? ",options:["You Die","Nothing","They become immune to Death Note","The Death Note losses its power"],answer:"They become immune to Death Note",id:384},{question:"In My Hero Academia, what is the name of Sir Nighteye's protege (Hint: Quirk-Permeation)",options:["Mirio Togata","Mei Hatsume","Tamaki Amajiki","Nejire Hado"],answer:"Mirio Togata",id:385}];var g=[{question:"What is alterego of ironman",options:["Tony Stark","Steve Rodgers","Robert Downey jr","Pepper potts"],answer:"Tony Stark",id:221},{question:"What is alterego of Black Panther",options:["T'chaka","T'chala","Shuri","Felicia"],answer:"T'chala",id:222},{question:"What is element used in Captain America's Shield",options:["Adamantium","Vibranium","element X","Kryptonite"],answer:"Vibranium",id:223},{question:"What is alterego of Spiderman",options:["Tony Stark","Steve Rodgers","Robert Downey jr","Peter Parker"],answer:"Peter Parker",id:224},{question:"What is alterego of Venom",options:["Tony Stark","Tom Hardy","Eddie Brock","Peter Parker"],answer:"Eddie Brock",id:225},{question:"Who is father of Thor",options:["Odin","Loki","Destroyer","Heimdall"],answer:"Odin",id:226},{question:"What is name of Thor's Hammer",options:["Mjolnir","Myolnir","Miolnir","Mia mia"],answer:"Mjolnir",id:227},{question:"What is alterego of Hawkeye",options:["Clint Barton","Tom Hardy","Sam Wilson","Wilson fisk"],answer:"Clint Barton",id:228},{question:"What is alterego of Hulk",options:["Bruce wayne","Carol danvers","Bruce Banner","Hulk Buster"],answer:"Bruce Banner",id:229},{question:"Which radiation caused te creation of Hulk",options:["cosmic","Gamma","InfraRed","Alpha"],answer:"Gamma",id:230}],k=[{question:"What is alterego of Scarlet Witch",options:["Wanda Maximoff","vanda maximaff","wanda maxximoff","Wanda maximaff"],answer:"Wanda Maximoff",id:251},{question:"What is Father of Iron Man?",options:["Howard Duck","Howard Stark","Henry Stark","Morgan Stark"],answer:"Howard Stark",id:252},{question:"What is alterego of Human Torch",options:["Johnny Storm","Albert Storm","Harry Storm","Sue Storm"],answer:"Johnny Storm",id:253},{question:"What is alterego of Mr.Fantastic?",options:["Reed Richards","Reed Hollands","Johnny richards","Rory Stark"],answer:"Reed Richards",id:254},{question:"What is Color of Time Stone",options:["Orange","Red","Emerald","Yellow"],answer:"Emerald",id:255},{question:"Who is son of Thanos",options:["Thane","Tanatos","deathracer","Deadpool"],answer:"Thane",id:256},{question:"What is alter ego of the Lizard",options:["Dr.summers","Dr.connors","Dr.richards","Dr.smith"],answer:"Dr.connors",id:257},{question:"Where is the head quaters of Avengers located?",options:["Mount Rushmore","Nanda Parbat","Manhattan","New york"],answer:"New york",id:258},{question:"How many Legendary rings that mandarin possess?",options:["Six","Eight","Ten","Seven"],answer:"Ten",id:259},{question:"What is name of first AI in iron man's suit?",options:["Friday","orion","Jarvis","Aida"],answer:"Jarvis",id:260}],y=[{question:"What is alterego of Hob Globin ?",options:["Roderick Kingsley","Norman Osborn","Harry osborn","Flash Thompson"],answer:"Roderick Kingsley",id:281},{question:"Who is the Gaurdian of Web of Destiny?",options:["Madame Xunadu","Madame web","Ancient one","Heimdall"],answer:"Madame web",id:282},{question:"Who is the Unstoppable mutant ?",options:["Wolverine","Quicksilver","Jaggernaut","Deadpool"],answer:"Jaggernaut",id:283},{question:"What is alterego of Black Cat?",options:["Felicia Hardy","Mary jane","Gwen Stacy","Selina kyle"],answer:"Felicia Hardy",id:284},{question:"Who is archnemesis of Hulk?",options:["Red Hulk","Armageddon","red she-hulk","Allwiow"],answer:"Armageddon",id:285},{question:"What is the alterego of Mr.Sinister?",options:["Remy Etienne LeBeau","Remy Emienne LeBeau","sam Etienne LeBeau","Ramy LeBeau"],answer:"Remy Etienne LeBeau",id:286},{question:"Who cursed Deadpool with immortality?",options:["Thanos","Wolverine","Death","weapon x"],answer:"Thanos",id:287},{question:"What is alterego of DareDevil?",options:["Matt Murdack","Matt Murdock","Luke cage","Matthew Richards"],answer:"Matt Murdock",id:288},{question:"What is alterego of doctor strange?",options:["Stephen Strange","Rick Strange","Steaven Strange","Richard Strange"],answer:"Stephen Strange",id:289},{question:"Who is Arch-nemesis of Daredevil?",options:["Wilson Fisk","Punisher","Luke cage","The Beyonder"],answer:"Wilson Fisk",id:290}];var q=[{question:"What is Family name of Levi",options:["Ackerman","Akermaan","Ackarmon","Ackerman"],answer:"Ackerman",id:421},{question:"Along with Eren, who was shot and tranquilized in the back of a wagon?",options:["Mikasa","Historia","Shasha","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:422},{question:"Who was the only Reiss family member to visit Historia on the farm?",options:["Uri","Drick","Florian","Frieda"],answer:"Frieda",id:423},{question:"Who is the shortest soilder of 104th cadet",options:["Eren","Mikasa","Armin","Historia"],answer:"Historia",id:424},{question:"What is name of the civil war within the empire?",options:["War of Giants","Great Titan War","Black eldien","Great Eldien War"],answer:"Great Titan War",id:425},{question:"Who is responsible for maintaining order within the internment zones such as Liberio?",options:["Survey corps","Marley police","Marley public security","kingsgaurd"],answer:"Marley public security",id:426},{question:"Eren gained Hardening after consuming a bottle labelled?",options:["Hardening","Confidential","Deflection","Armor"],answer:"Armor",id:427},{question:"What is Eren's Titan Form called?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:428},{question:"Who is the slowest Titan",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Colossal Titan",id:429},{question:"Which Titan has the hardest skin?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Armored Titan",id:430}],A=[{question:"Armin confiscated what from Marlo and Hitch?",options:["Food","Supplies","Rifles","Info"],answer:"Rifles",id:451},{question:"What is Symbol of Eldiens",options:["White band","Tattoos","Shorts","Gears"],answer:"White band",id:452},{question:"Who saved Hange from Cart titan",options:["Jean","Eren","Mikasa","Armin"],answer:"Jean",id:453},{question:"Who saved Mikasa from the Titans",options:["Attack Titan","Female titan","Armored Titan","Armin"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:454},{question:"Who is commander of survey corps?",options:["Erwin","levi","Armin","Mikasa"],answer:"Erwin",id:455},{question:"Who almost killed the beast titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Levi",id:456},{question:"Who became the new colossal titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Armin",id:457},{question:"Who became the new jaw titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Ymir","Armin"],answer:"Ymir",id:458},{question:"Who is Scientist researching on Titans?",options:["Hange","Ymir","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Hange",id:459},{question:"Who stopped Annie escape from the fight with Eren?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Mikasa",id:460}],v=[{question:"What is the name of island in Attack on Titan?",options:["Ellis island","Paradis island","Funen island","Elldian island"],answer:"Paradis island",id:481},{question:"Who of the 104th Cadet Corps has been referred to as \u201cGoddess\u201d?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:482},{question:"Which character has their ears turn red when they lie?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Eren",id:483},{question:"How many Titan Shifters are there in AOT?",options:["Six","Ten","Nine","Eleven"],answer:"Nine",id:484},{question:"Which Titan Shifter can maintain their titan form only for short period ?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Colossal",id:485},{question:"Who saved armin from Titan's mouth?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Levi"],answer:"Eren",id:486},{question:"What is Annie\u2019s last name?",options:["Reiss","Lonarld","Leonhart","Tierce"],answer:"Leonhart",id:487},{question:"What is life span of Titan shifters",options:["9 years","15 years","13 years","12 years"],answer:"13 years",id:488},{question:"Who did Ymir eat to return to her human form?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Jaw",id:489},{question:"Which gear is used in fight of retake maria",options:["Anti personnal uni-directional","3d manuer gear","Breach Cannons","Anti personnal omni-directional"],answer:"Anti personnal omni-directional",id:490}];var W=[{question:"What is alterego of Nine Tails Fox",options:["Red Demon Fox","Kurama","Shukaku","Matatabi"],answer:"Kurama",id:521},{question:"Whom did Naruto kiss first?",options:["Sasuke Uchiha","Hinata Hyuga","Fuka","Sakura Haruno"],answer:"Sasuke Uchiha",id:522},{question:"With whose fight did Naruto first use Nine tails Chakra?",options:["Sasuke","Neji","Haku","Gaara"],answer:"Haku",id:523},{question:"Who tricked Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?",options:["Iruka","Mizuki","Sasuke","Zabuza"],answer:"Mizuki",id:524},{question:"What is another word for ninja?",options:["Genjutsu","Shinobi","Arigato","Chakra"],answer:"Shinobi",id:525},{question:"Which of the legendary sannin becomes the fifth Hokage?",options:["Jiraya","Tsunade","Orochimaru","Kakashi"],answer:"Tsunade",id:526},{question:"Who was the first ninja Sasuke Uchiha copied with the Sharingan?",options:["Rock Lee","Itachi Uchiha","Orochimaru","Naruto"],answer:"Rock Lee",id:527},{question:"Which famous clan was completely massacred?",options:["Uchiha","Hyuuga","Uzamaki","Nara"],answer:"Uchiha",id:528},{question:"What piece of jewelry do the Akatsuki wear?",options:["Earrings","Nose rings","Rings","Anklets"],answer:"Rings",id:529},{question:"What is the village where Naruto lives called?",options:["Sunagakure","Kyuubigakure","Uzamagakure","Konohagakure"],answer:"Konohagakure",id:530}],S=[{question:"How many ninja from Konoha went on to the third stage(after the preliminairies) of the Chunin Exams?",options:["Six","Five","Seven","Four"],answer:"Five",id:551},{question:"What's the name of the leader of the toads?",options:["Wise Frog Master","Giant Toad King","Master Froggo","Great Toad Sage"],answer:"Great Toad Sage",id:552},{question:"How did Hidan (one of the Akatsuki member) die?",options:["He can't die","He was starved","He was trapped in Shadow Posession Jutsu while Ino and Choji killed him","His own god betrayed him"],answer:"He can't die",id:553},{question:"Who gave their life to save Gaara?",options:["Kankuro","Sasori","Chiyo","Fugi"],answer:"Chiyo",id:554},{question:"Who created the Akatsuki?",options:["Orochimar","Tobi","Itachi","Yahiko"],answer:"Yahiko",id:555},{question:"What is Minato's nickname?",options:["The Yellow Flash","The Red Flash","Flash Ninja","Flash of the Leaf"],answer:"The Yellow Flash",id:556},{question:"Which member joined team Taka/Hebi first?",options:["Karin","Jugo","Suigetsu","They all joined at the same time"],answer:"Suigetsu",id:557},{question:"What is Kakashi/Obito's Sharingan ability?",options:["Tsukuyomi","Amaterasu","Kotoamatsukami","Kamui"],answer:"Kamui",id:558},{question:"What was Zabuza's nickname?",options:["The demon of the hidden mist","The silent killer","The demonic killer","The monster of the mist"],answer:"The demon of the hidden mist",id:559},{question:"What is Tsunade's addiction?",options:["Men","Gambling","Work","Alcohol"],answer:"Gambling",id:560}],T=[{question:"In Naruto, what is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",options:["Lotus of Destruction","Shadow Lotus","Primary Lotus","Fiery Lotus"],answer:"Primary Lotus",id:581},{question:"What does ANBU mean?",options:["Special Unit Forces and Recruits","Special Assassination and Tactical Squad","Undercover Ninjas: Black Operations","Hidden Agendas of Shinobi and Allied Tactics"],answer:"Special Assassination and Tactical Squad",id:582},{question:"How did Sakumo Hatake (Kakashi's father) die?",options:["He got killed on a mission","He was killed by Madara","He naturally died of old age","He committed suicide"],answer:"He committed suicide",id:583},{question:"Who were the first reincarnates of Indra and Ashura?",options:["Naruto and Sasuke","Madara and Hashirama","Sasuke and Itachi","Kakashi and Guy"],answer:"Madara and Hashirama",id:584},{question:"Who was the youngest Jonin?",options:["Kakashi","Itachi","Neji","Sakura"],answer:"Kakashi",id:585},{question:"What does Gaara's tattoo mean?",options:["Orphan","Monster","Love","Hate"],answer:"Love",id:586},{question:"What is Sasuke's team called?",options:["Tiki","Taka","Toka","Toku"],answer:"Taka",id:587},{question:"Which of these characters has Kurama's chakra?",options:["Menma","Guren","Sora","Haku"],answer:"Sora",id:588},{question:"Which of them is not a Kekkei Genkai?",options:["Particle style","Byakugan","Sharingan","Tenseigan"],answer:"Particle style",id:589},{question:"Who is not part of the Team Kurenai?",options:["Shino","Kiba","Hinata","Neji"],answer:"Neji",id:590}];var b=[{question:"Izuku Midoriya is also known as:",options:["All Might","Endeavor","Deku","Stendhal"],answer:"Deku",id:621},{question:"What is a \u201cquirk\u201d?",options:["a hero","a superpower","a battle","an event"],answer:"a superpower",id:622},{question:"How did Izuku Midoriya got his powers?",options:["Eats hair","Trains really hard","Five hour energy","Tons of steroids"],answer:"Eats hair",id:623},{question:"Who is Number one hero?",options:["Midnight","Cementross","No. 13","All Might"],answer:"All Might",id:624},{question:"What is the opposite of One for All?",options:["None for All","All for One","Anti power","One in All"],answer:"All for One",id:625},{question:"What is All Might's quirk called?",options:["One For All","All For One","Super punchy power","One Strong Boi"],answer:"One For All",id:626},{question:"Who does All Might, the world's greatest hero, pass his powers to? ",options:["Tenya","Kashuki","Izuku","Tsugu"],answer:"Izuku",id:627},{question:"What school does Izuku dream of having powers and attending as a child?",options:["UD High","UA High","UC High","UB High"],answer:"UA High",id:628},{question:"What is Aizawa's hero name?",options:["Eraser Head","Reset Head","Restarted","Disabler Head"],answer:"Eraser Head",id:629},{question:"What does Izuku call his childhood friend as?",options:["Bakugo","Katsuki","Baku","Kacchan"],answer:"Kacchan",id:630}],M=[{question:"What is All Might\u2019s real name?",options:["Enji Todoroki","Chizome Akaguro","Toshinori Yagi","Ochaco Uraraka"],answer:"Toshinori Yagi",id:651},{question:"What is Endeavor's original name?",options:["Shinji Nishiya","Enji Todoroki","Sorahiko","Sir Nighteye"],answer:"Enji Todoroki",id:652},{question:"Who is the class president of Class-A? ",options:["Tenya ilda","Bakugo","Todiroki","Midoriya"],answer:"Tenya ilda",id:653},{question:"Who is Class-A teacher?",options:["midnight","Aizawa","nezu","All Might"],answer:"Aizawa",id:654},{question:"Which characters hero name is Uravity?",options:["Uraraka Ochaco","Izuku Mydoria","Tenya ilda","Todiroki shouto"],answer:"Uraraka Ochaco",id:655},{question:"What quirk does Kasuki Bakugo have?",options:["One for all","Dark Shadow","Erasing","Explosion"],answer:"Explosion",id:656},{question:"Who runs the Infirmary at UA high?",options:["Hiroshi Shinso","Mashirao Ojiro","Recovery Girl","Fumikage Tokoyami"],answer:"Recovery Girl",id:657},{question:"What is Shigaraki Tomura quirk?",options:["Strength","Teleportation","Hands","Disintegration"],answer:"Disintegration",id:658},{question:"What punch does All Might use to defeat All For One?",options:["American Smash","Global Smash","Ultimate Smash","United States Of Smash"],answer:"United States Of Smash",id:659},{question:"How many students are in class-A?",options:["19","18","20","21"],answer:"20",id:660}],E=[{question:"Which successor of One For All is Izuku Midoriya?",options:["7th","8th","9th","10th"],answer:"9th",id:681},{question:"Who is the rubber like villain that All Might fought at the training camp?",options:["Nezu","Nomu","Tomura Shigaraki","Kurogiri"],answer:"Kurogiri",id:682},{question:"What was hero killer stain's Quirk ability?",options:["freezing people","blades strikes","flying","being a scary boi"],answer:"freezing people",id:683},{question:"What did the doctor say was responsible for Izuku not getting his quirk?",options:["Two joints on his pinky toe","A hole in his heart","An injury on his leg","A fractured elbow"],answer:"Two joints on his pinky toe",id:684},{question:"What job did All Might initially suggest to Izuku since he wanted to save people?",options:["A Soldier","A Policeman","A Doctor","An Ambulance Driver"],answer:"A Policeman",id:685},{question:"Where does Izuku train, in order to be able to receive All Might's power?",options:["Dogobah Municipal Memorial Park","Dogobah Municipal Football Stadium","Dogobah Municipal Play Park","Dogobah Municipal Beach Park"],answer:"Dogobah Municipal Beach Park",id:686},{question:"For how long does Izuku train to inherit All Might's quirk?",options:["2 Years","10 Months","6 Months","1 week"],answer:"10 Months",id:687},{question:"Which of these superheroes is Tenya's brother?",options:["Kurogiri","Tamura","Nomu","Ingenium"],answer:"Ingenium",id:688},{question:"What does Izuku Midoriya's nickname Deku mean?",options:["world's greatest hero","chimp","It means nothing","one who can't achieve/do anything"],answer:"one who can't achieve/do anything",id:689},{question:"What's the name of the group within the League Of Villains that Dabi leads?",options:["Vanguard Attack Squad","Vanguard Action Squad","Frontier Action Squad","Frontier Attack Squad"],answer:"Vanguard Action Squad",id:690}];var H=["Sean Schemmel passed out while recording Goku's Super Saiyan level 4 transformation for Dragon Ball GT.","Yoshihiro Togashi, the creator of Hunter X Hunter, is married to the creator of Sailor Moon, Naoko Takeuchi.","Sixty Percent Of The World's Animation Is Anime","The Titans in 'Attack On Titan' Are Based On Drunks","Everyone In 'Code Geass' Loves Pizza Because The Series Was Funded By Pizza Hut","50 New Colors Were Created For 'Akira'","'Spirited Away' Is The First Anime To Win An Academy Award","The Authors Of 'Sailor Moon' And 'Yu Yu Hakusho' Are Married","'Bleach' Almost Didn't Happen","'Death Note' Inspired Chinese Children To Write Down The Names Of Their Teachers"," Eucliwood Hellscythe Anime Character Has 10 Different Voices","'Your Name' Is The Highest Grossing Anime Film Worldwide","Studio Ghibli Is Named After A WWII-Era Aircraft","'Sazae-san' Is The Longest Running Animated TV Series","The First Magical Girl Anime Aired In The '60s","Real-Life Japanese Astronaut Recorded His 'Space Brothers' Cameo From The ISS","'Naruto' Characters Inspired By Japanese Film Industry"];var D=["Superman was supposed to be a bald character, obsessed with dominating the world.","We know that the Hulk is green. But did you know that originally the Hulk was supposed to be grey in colour? Since green looked better in print, the colour of the Hulk was changed to green.","Superman is a vegetarian. Before 2005 the writers of Superman did not think about this. Since Superman\u2019s senses are sharper than a human\u2019s, he is aware of when a life aura ends. So, he was made a vegetarian.","Remember Michael Jackson? He came very close to owning Marvel Comics because he wanted to play the role of Spider-man. We would have had a break-dancing Spidey then!","We have all been fascinated by Superman\u2019s good looks and his dark hair. But Superman was supposed to be a bald character, obsessed with dominating the world.","Captain America\u2019s Shield beats up villains and provides justice. However, this round shaped shield was originally supposed to be heraldic-shaped. Since this was in use by a patriotic character of a rival comic, Captain America\u2019s shield was made round.","What if your favourite X-men character, Wolverine was to be named after a rodent? Yes, Wolverine was originally the Badger who was supposed to battle with the Hulk.","The 2009 Amazing Spider-man comic has Spidey meet President Barrack Obama, and they even share a fist bump.","Who is Batman\u2019s favourite enemy? Yes, the Joker. The Joker was supposed to die just after the first Batman series. But writers saw potential in the villain and brought him back to mess around with Batman.","Wonder Woman was made out of clay by her mother and was brought to life by the Greek Gods.","In 1989, Marvel comics introduced a superhero whose only superpower was that he couldn\u2019t die, Mr. Immortal. He tried killing himself, but was unsuccessful every time."];var C=function(e){Object(l.a)(i,e);var a=Object(u.a)(i);function i(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(t=a.call(this,e)).selected=function(e){var a=[];a.push(e.target.value),t.setState({options:a,click:!0}),a[0]===t.state.answer?t.setState({color:"green"}):t.setState({color:"red"}),t.props.selection(a[0])},t.state={question:e.question,options:e.options,answer:e.answer,click:!1},t}return Object(h.a)(i,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-4 m-2"},n.a.createElement("h2",null,this.state.question),this.state.options.map((function(a,i){return n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-dark m-2",disabled:e.state.click,style:{backgroundColor:"".concat(e.state.color)},key:i,value:a,onClick:e.selected},a)})))}}]),i}(n.a.Component),N=function(e){Object(l.a)(i,e);var a=Object(u.a)(i);function i(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(t=a.call(this,e)).changetopic=function(e){t.props.settopic(e.target.value)},t.changedifficulty=function(e){t.props.setdifficulty(e.target.value)},t.getquizquestions=function(){t.props.startquiz()},t.changegenre=function(e){t.props.setgenre(e.target.value),t.setState({genre:e.target.value})},t.state={topic:e.topic,difficulty:e.difficulty,genre:e.genre},t}return Object(h.a)(i,[{key:"render",value:function(){return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"GENRE:"),n.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changegenre},n.a.createElement("option",{value:"comics"},"Comics"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"Anime"},"Anime"))),n.a.createElement("div",null,"comics"===this.state.genre?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center"},n.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},n.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"TOPIC:"),n.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changetopic},n.a.createElement("option",{value:"DC"},"DC"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"MARVEL"},"MARVEL"))),n.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},n.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"DIFFICULTY : "),n.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changedifficulty},n.a.createElement("option",{value:"easy"},"EASY"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"moderate"},"MODERATE"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"hard"},"HARD"))),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary lg-col-4 sm-col-12 p-2 m-3",onClick:this.getquizquestions},"Start Quiz")):null),n.a.createElement("div",null,"Anime"===this.state.genre?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center"},n.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},n.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"TOPIC:"),n.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changetopic},n.a.createElement("option",{value:"AOT"},"ATTACK ON TITAN"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"NARUTO"},"NARUTO"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"MHA"},"MY HERO ACADEMIA"))),n.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},n.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"DIFFICULTY : "),n.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changedifficulty},n.a.createElement("option",{value:"easy"},"EASY"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"moderate"},"MODERATE"),n.a.createElement("option",{value:"hard"},"HARD"))),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary lg-col-4 sm-col-12 p-2 m-3",onClick:this.getquizquestions},"Start Quiz")):null),n.a.createElement("div",null," "))}}]),i}(n.a.Component),F=function(e){Object(l.a)(i,e);var a=Object(u.a)(i);function i(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(t=a.call(this,e)).state={timer:e.initialtimer,tclass:"badge badge-success timer m-4"},t}return Object(h.a)(i,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=this;this.timer=setInterval((function(){e.setState({timer:e.state.timer-1}),e.state.timer<11&&e.setState({tclass:"badge badge-danger timer m-4"}),0==e.state.timer&&(e.setState({timer:60}),e.props.timeout())}),1e3)}},{key:"componentWillUnmount",value:function(){clearInterval(this.timer)}},{key:"render",value:function(){return n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("h2",{className:this.state.tclass},"Time Left : ",this.state.timer))}}]),i}(n.a.Component),B=function(e){Object(l.a)(i,e);var a=Object(u.a)(i);function i(e){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(t=a.call(this,e)).getsolution=function(e,a){t.state.responses<5&&(e===a&&t.setState({score:t.state.score+10}),t.setState({responses:t.state.responses+1}))},t.state={questions:[],responses:0,topic:"DC",difficult:"easy",score:0,settimer:!1,timer:60,genre:"comics",quote:""},t}return Object(h.a)(i,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.refresher()}},{key:"refresher",value:function(){this.setState({questions:[],responses:0,topic:"DC",difficulty:"easy",score:0,settimer:!1,timer:60,genre:"comics",quote:""})}},{key:"changegenre",value:function(e){this.setState({genre:e}),"comics"==e&&this.setState({topic:"DC",difficult:"easy"}),"Anime"==e&&this.setState({topic:"AOT",difficult:"easy"}),"Movies"==e&&this.setState({topic:"Harry Potter",difficult:"easy"})}},{key:"changetopic",value:function(e){this.setState({topic:e})}},{key:"changedifficulty",value:function(e){this.setState({difficulty:e})}},{key:"getquizquestions",value:function(){var e=this.state.topic,a=[];if("DC"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(d[n[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(c[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(m[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"MARVEL"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(g[n[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(k[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(y[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"ANIME"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(p[n[s]]),console.log(p[n[s]].question);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(f[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(w[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"AOT"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(q[n[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(A[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(v[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"NARUTO"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(W[n[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(S[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(T[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"MHA"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,t=[],n=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=n.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=n[--o],n[o]=n[i],n[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)t.push(b[n[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)t.push(M[n[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var h=0;h<5;h++)t.push(E[n[h]]);return t}(this.state.difficulty)),"comics"==this.state.genre){var i=D[Math.floor(Math.random()*D.length)];this.setState({quote:i})}if("Anime"==this.state.genre){var t=H[Math.floor(Math.random()*H.length)];this.setState({quote:t})}this.setState({questions:a,responses:0,settimer:!0,timer:60})}},{key:"timeout",value:function(){this.setState({timer:60,settimer:!1,responses:5})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},n.a.createElement("div",null,0===this.state.responses?n.a.createElement(N,{Box:!0,topic:this.state.topic,genre:this.state.genre,difficulty:this.state.diffulty,settopic:function(a){return e.changetopic(a)},setdifficulty:function(a){return e.changedifficulty(a)},startquiz:function(){return e.getquizquestions()},setgenre:function(a){return e.changegenre(a)}}):null),n.a.createElement("div",null,!0===this.state.settimer&&this.state.responses<5?n.a.createElement(F,{initialtimer:this.state.timer,timeout:function(){return e.timeout()}}):null),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"Quizarea"},this.state.questions.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questions.map((function(a){var i=a.question,t=a.options,o=a.answer,s=a.id;return n.a.createElement(C,{question:i,options:t,key:s,answer:o,selection:function(a){return e.getsolution(a,o)}})})),5===this.state.responses?n.a.createElement("div",null,n.a.createElement("h2",{className:"p-2"},"Your Score"),n.a.createElement("h1",{className:"p-2"},this.state.score,"/50"),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary m-2",onClick:function(){return e.refresher()}},"Retake Quiz"),n.a.createElement("h2",{className:"fact"},this.state.genre," fun-fact:",n.a.createElement("br",null),'"',this.state.quote,'" ')):null))}}]),i}(n.a.Component);var R=function(){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},n.a.createElement(B,null))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));s.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(R,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}],[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f542efc1.chunk.js.map